https://www.reedssports.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

The store will not work correctly in the case when cookies are disabled.
Reeds store locations
Ice Fishing & Holiday Savings! Use Code ICE2020 on Flagged Products!
New Winter Hours: Our Retail Stores are open Wednesday - Sunday.
Call Center is open 7 days a week!
FirearmsShotgunsOver & UnderPumpBoltSide by SideSingle ShotSemi-AutoCompactRiflesSemi-AutoBoltCompactLeverSingle ShotRevolverHandgunsSemi-AutoRevolverSingle ShotBlack PowderRifleHandgunAmmunitionShotgunHandgunCenterfireRimfireAirgunsHunting & TrapOpticsBinocularsScopesRangefindersGame CamerasSightsAccessoriesDecoys & CallsDecoysBags & StorageCallsAccessoriesBlinds & StandsBlindsStandsDogAccessoriesHunting GearPacksTools & KnivesArcheryProcessing Tools & GearDogScents & AttractantsBags & StorageShooting GearHolstersStorage & SafesAirguns & AccessoriesSafety & Hearing ProtectionTargetsCases & BagsAccessoriesFishingElectronicsSonar, GPS & CombosUnder Water CamerasLake Map SoftwareBatteries & ChargersDownriggersAccessoriesTrolling Motors & GearTransom Mount MotorsBow Mount MotorsEngine Mount MotorsBoat Anchoring SystemsAccessoriesMarine AccessoriesStorageBoat & Motor CareAnchoring, Rope & DockingLighting & AccessoriesTraileringAccessoriesMapsBoat ControlRods, Reels & CombosRodsReelsCombosAccessoriesTackle & StorageTackle, Jigs & LineTackle StorageLive Bait CareOpen Water GearLife Vests SafetyToolsFish CleaningNetsAccessoriesIce FishingElectronicsFlashers & SonarUnder Water CamerasHandheld DepthfindersMaps & ChartsAccessoriesFish HousesFlip-Over SheltersHub Style SheltersSledsAccessoriesAugersGas Power AugersElectric AugersPropane Power AugersHand AugersRods, Reels & TackleRodsReelsCombosTackle, Jigs & LineAccessoriesOn Ice GearHeatersToolsStorageFish CleaningRattle Reels & Tip-UpsAccessoriesIce ApparelIce SuitsIce JacketsIce Bibs & PantsAccessoriesLogo WearWatersportsPaddle SportsKayaksCanoesStand Up Paddle BoardsPaddlesLife VestsAccessoriesWatersportsTowables & FloatsWater ToysWater PlatformsKnee BoardsWater SkisWake SurfsWake BoardsLife VestsAccessoriesCamping & CookingCookingCookwareCoolersGrills & SmokersDeep FryersSeasons, Sauces & RubsDrinkwareAccessoriesCampingFurnitureBags & LuggageToys & GamesSleepingTents & StorageAccessoriesOutdoor GearCoolersPower ToolsDrinkwareCamerasKnivesLightsToys & GamesHomeGardenApparelMen'sShirts & TopsPants & ShortsVests & PulloversLogo WearJackets, Coats & OuterwearHats & CapsGloves & MittsBaselayerAccessoriesSwimwearWomen'sShirts & TopsPants & ShortsDresses & SkirtsLogo WearJackets, Coats & OuterwearHats & CapsGloves & MittsBaselayerAccessoriesSwimwearKid'sShirts & TopsPants & ShortsDresses & SkirtsLogo WearJackets, Coats & OuterwearHats & CapsGloves & MittsBaselayerAccessoriesSwimwearIce ApparelIce SuitsIce JacketsIce Bibs & PantsAccessoriesLogo WearAccessoriesPurses & BagsSunglassesBelts & SuspendersFootwearMen'sCasualBootsWadersSandals & WatershoesSocksWomen'sCasualBootsWadersSandals & WatershoesSocksKid'sInfantToddlerYouthSandals & WatershoesSocksAccessoriesShoe & Boot CareStorageLacesInsolesDryers & HeatersSocks
Brands
Home
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
At Reeds, we want you to know how we collect, use, share, and protect information about you. By interacting with Reeds through our stores, websites, and mobile applications, you consent to the use of information that is collected or submitted as described in this privacy policy. We may change or add to this privacy policy, so we encourage you to review it periodically.
What Information Is Collected?
Types of information we collect may include:
Name
Mailing address
E-mail address
Phone (or mobile) number
Date of birth or age
Driver’s license number
Credit/debit card number
Purchase/return/exchange information
Registry or list information
Your mobile device information (e.g., device model, operating system version, device date and time, unique device identifiers, mobile network information)
How you use our sites and mobile applications, search terms, pages you visit on our mobile applications, and application performance, as discussed further below
Geo-location and in-store location (with your consent)
Facebook ID, profile picture, gender, age range, friends' IDs (with your consent)
Google ID, profile picture (with your consent)
If you choose not to provide information we may not be able to provide you with requested products, services or information.
Automated Information Collection
We may connect information collected automatically with information we already have about you in order to identify you as a Reeds guest. If we are able to identify you as a Reeds guest we may, for example, link your activity on our website to your activity in a Reeds store or on one of our mobile applications. This allows us to provide you with a personalized experience regardless of how you interact with us – online, in store, mobile, etc.
In order to provide the best guest experience possible, we also use automated information collection technologies for reporting and analysis purposes. We examine metrics such as how you are shopping on our website, in our stores, and on our mobile applications, the performance of our marketing efforts, and your response to those marketing efforts.
Reeds Automated Collection
We and our service providers use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us through your computer or mobile device. This information, which includes, but is not limited to: the pages you visit on our site or mobile application, which web address you came from, the type of browser/device/hardware you are using, purchase information and checkout process, search terms, and IP-based geographic location, helps us recognize you, customize your website experience and make our marketing messages more relevant. This includes Reeds content presented on another website or mobile application, for example, Reeds Weekly Ad. These technologies also enable us to provide features such as storage of items in your cart between visits and Short Message Service (SMS)/text messages you have chosen to receive. We also use Flash cookies for fraud prevention purposes.
Third-Party Automated Collection and Interest-Based Advertising
Reeds participates in interest-based advertising (IBA), also known as Online Behavioral Advertising. We use third-party advertising companies to display ads tailored to your individual interests based on how you browse and shop online. Reeds adheres to the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) self-regulatory principles for IBA.
We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our websites or use our mobile applications. This information is used to serve ads for Reeds products or services or for the products or services of other companies when you visit this website or other websites. These companies use non-personally-identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, hardware/software information, cookie and session ID) and personally identifiable information (e.g., static IP address) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These parties typically use a cookie, web beacon, or other similar tracking technologies to collect this information.
Our Do Not Track Policy
Some browsers have a "do not track" feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. At this time, we do not respond to browser "do not track" signals, but we do provide you the option to opt out of interest based advertising. To learn more about IBA or to opt-out of this type of advertising, visit the Network Advertising Initiative website and the Digital Advertising Alliance website. Options you select are browser and device-specific.
User Experience Information
In order to improve guest online and mobile shopping experiences, help with fraud identification, and assist our guest relations representatives in resolving issues guests may experience in completing online purchases, we use tools to monitor certain user experience information; including login information, IP address, data regarding pages visited and ads clicked, specific actions taken on pages visited (e.g. information entered during checkout process), and browser information.
Social Media
Reeds engages with guests on multiple social media platforms (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, and Pinterest). If you contact us on one of our social media platforms, or request guest service via social media we may contact you via direct message. In these instances, your interactions with us are governed by this privacy policy as well as the privacy policy of the social media platform you use.
Social Media Widgets
Our sites and mobile applications include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, Google Plus, Pinterest, and Twitter widgets. These features may collect information about your IP address and which page you’re visiting on our site, and they may set a cookie or employ other tracking technologies. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with those features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.
Information from Other Sources
We collect data that’s publicly available. For example, the information you submit in a public forum (e.g., a blog, chat room, or social network) can be read, collected or used by us and others, and could be used to personalize your experience. You are responsible for the information you choose to submit in these instances.
We also obtain information provided by third parties. For instance, we obtain information from companies that can enhance our existing guest information to improve the accuracy and add to the information we have about our guests (e.g., adding address information).This improves our ability to contact you and increases the relevance of our marketing by providing better product recommendations or special offers that may interest you.
Store Cameras
We use cameras in and around our stores for security purposes and for operational purposes such as measuring traffic patterns and tracking in-stock levels.
How Is Your Information Used?
Examples of how we use the information we collect include:
Product and Service Fulfillment
Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, and returns/exchanges
Respond to requests for information about our products and services in our stores, or on our website, mobile website, or mobile applications or to otherwise serve you
Connect with you regarding guest service via our contact center, guest service desk, or on social media or internet chat platforms
Provide services such as Gift Registry or a shopping list
Administer sweepstakes and contests
Conduct a transaction where we collect information required by law (for example, pseudoephedrine or age-restricted purchases)
Allow you to, using our mobile applications: find a store nearest to your location via Store Finder, show you a map of the store (if available), sign up for coupons, search for products and check availability, check prices, provide product ratings and reviews, track your orders, scan a UPC barcode or QR code, use voice recognition to add to your list, update information, etc.
Our Marketing Purposes
Deliver coupons, mobile coupons, newsletters, in-store receipt messages, e-mails, mobile messages, and social media notifications
Provide interactive features of the website or mobile applications, such as product reviews or Weekly Ad, send marketing communications and other information regarding products, services and promotions
Administer promotions, surveys, and focus groups
Internal Operations
Improve the effectiveness of our website, stores, mobile experience, and marketing efforts
Conduct research and analysis, including focus groups and surveys
Perform other business activities as needed, or as described elsewhere in this policy
Prevention of Fraud and Other Harm
Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft and otherwise protect our guests and our business (e.g. product recalls)
Legal Compliance
For example, assist law enforcement and respond to legal/regulatory inquiries
How Is Your Information Shared?
Reeds Subsidiaries and Affiliates
We share the information we collect within Reeds Family Outdoor Outfitters, which includes all Reeds subsidiaries and affiliates. Reeds Family Outdoor Outfitters may use this information to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you.
Reeds Family Outdoor Outfitters owns and operates Reeds Stores, websites, and mobile applications.
Service Providers
We may share the information we collect with companies that provide support services to us (such as printers, e-mail providers, mobile marketing services, analytics providers, web hosting providers, call center/chat providers, sweepstakes vendors, payment processors, coupon delivery vendors, data enhancement services, or fraud prevention providers) or that help us market our products and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions.
Legal Requirements
We may disclose information we collect when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law; to enforce or apply applicable terms and conditions and other agreements; to facilitate the financing, securitization, insuring, sale, assignment, bankruptcy, or disposal of all or part of our business or assets; or to protect the rights property or safety of our company, our guests or others.
Elsewhere at Your Direction
At your direction or request, or when you otherwise consent, we may share your information. For example, if you create a gift registry or shopping list and elect to make it available to the public, your information will be accessible on our website, mobile or social applications, and on kiosks in our stores.
Sharing with Other Companies (for their marketing purposes)
We may share your personal information with other companies, or organizations which are not part of Reeds. These companies and organizations may use the information we share to provide special offers and opportunities to you. To opt out of our sharing of your personal information with such companies and organizations, go to the Choices section of this privacy policy.
Sharing Non-identifiable or Aggregate Information with Third Parties
We may share non-identifiable or aggregate information with third parties for lawful purposes.
Business Transfers
In connection with the sale or transfer of some or all of our business assets, we may transfer the corresponding information regarding our guests. We also may retain a copy of that guest information.
What Choices Do You Have?
Postal Mail
If you do not wish to receive catalogs, coupons, and other promotional postal mail, email guest.relations@ReedsSports.com with your first and last name and complete mailing address or call 800-346-0019 to opt out.
Telephone
If you do not wish to receive promotional telephone calls, email guest.relations@ReedsSports.com with your first and last name and telephone number or call 800-346-0019 to opt out. This opt out does not apply to operational phone calls (e.g., confirmation of delivery address and prescription refills).
E-mail
If you do not wish to receive promotional e-mails from us, email guest.relations@ReedsSports.com or call 800-346-0019 to opt out. You may still receive select emails from us if you have requested them through one of our services such as Weekly Ad Reminders, Gift Reminders, or E-mail Me when Available notifications. You can discontinue these e-mails by canceling your subscription to these services.
You also have the ability to unsubscribe from promotional e-mails via the opt out link included in each promotional e-mail.
Sharing with Other Companies (for their marketing purposes)
If you do not wish us to share the personal information we have collected with other unaffiliated companies (for their marketing purposes), email this request to guest.relations@ReedsSports.com with your first and last name and complete mailing address or call 800-346-0019 to opt out.
Cookies, Tracking, and Interest-Based Advertising
The help function of your browser should contain instructions on how to set your computer to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued, or to not receive cookies at any time. If you set your device to not receive cookies at any time, certain personalized services cannot be provided to you, and accordingly, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our features (i.e. you will be able to browse the site, but will not be able to make a purchase).
Interest-Based Advertising
To opt out of interest-based advertising, visit the Network Advertising Initiative website and the Digital Advertising Alliance website.
Other Web Site Analytics Services
Analytics services such as Site Catalyst by Adobe Analytics and Google Analytics provide services that analyze information regarding visits to our websites and mobile applications. They use cookies, web beacons, and other tracking mechanisms to collect this information.
To learn about Adobe Analytics privacy practices or to opt out of cookies set to facilitate reporting, click here.
To learn more about Google’s privacy practices, click here. To access and use the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on, click here.
California Residents
If you are a California resident and have an established business relationship with us, you can request a notice disclosing the categories of personal information we have shared with third parties, for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, during the preceding calendar year. To request a notice, please submit your request to Reeds Family Outdoor Outfitters, Attn: California Shine the Light Inquiry, P.O. Box 490, Walker, MN 56484. Please allow 30 days for a response.
If you are a California resident under 18 years old and a registered user, you can request that we remove content or information that you have posted to our website or other online services. Note that fulfilment of the request may not ensure complete or comprehensive removal (e.g., if the content or information has been reposted by another user). To request removal of content or information, please email guest.relations@ReedsSports.com or call 800-346-0019.
How Do You Access and Update Your Personal Information?
In order to keep your personal information accurate and complete, you can access or update some of it in the following ways:
If you have created a Reeds.com account, you can log in to review and update your account information, including contact, billing, and shipping information.
Email guest.relations@ReedsSports.com or call 800-346-0019 with your current contact information and the personal information you would like to access. We will provide you the personal information requested if reasonably available, or will describe the types of personal information we typically collect.
How Is Your Personal Information Protected?
Security Methods
We maintain administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to protect your personal information. When we collect or transmit sensitive information such as a credit or debit card number, we use industry standard methods to protect that information. However, no e-commerce solution, website, mobile application, database or system is completely secure or "hacker proof." You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse.
E-mail Security
"Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an e-mail that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, username, credit card information, or other personal information through e-mail.
Children’s Personal Information
We recognize the particular importance of protecting privacy where children are involved. We do not knowingly collect personal information online from children under the age of 13. If a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information online, we ask that a parent or guardian email guest.relations@ReedsSports.com or call 800-346-0019.
How Do You Contact Reeds?
Mail:Reeds Family Outdoor OutfittersPO Box 490Walker, MN 56484
Phone: 800-346-0019
E-mail: guest.relations@ReedsSports.com
Reeds Privacy Policy Scope
This privacy policy applies to all current or former guest personal information, except for information collected by or provided in connection with:
Use of Reeds’s Wireless Service. See the Reeds Wireless Service Privacy Policy.
Completing of an application for employment with Reeds.
Our website may offer links to other sites. If you visit one of these sites, you may want to review the privacy policy on that site. In addition, you may have visited our website through a link or a banner advertisement on another site. In such cases, the site you linked from may collect information from people who click on the banner or link. You may want to refer to the privacy policies on those sites to see how they collect and use this information.List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie Name
Cookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
You have no items in your wish list.
© 1999-2020 Reeds Family Outdoor Outfitters
